missionfed.com 2011-10-11

# Privacy Policy | Mission Federal Credit Union, San Diego County | Your credit union for checking, savings, auto & home loans in San Diego.

## Your Privacy is Secure at Mission Fed

As your credit union, we take your privacy very seriously and we safeguard it at every step. Our strict Privacy Policy keeps your personal information secure. Every Mission Fed employee receives training to ensure this.

If you have any questions about Mission Fed's Privacy Policy, please email or call us at 800.500.6328.

If you wish to opt out of information sharing with our affiliates (companies we own or control) please email us at [optout@missionfed.com](mailto:optout@missionfed.com).

**Privacy Policy**  
Mission Federal Credit Union (Mission Fed) is committed to earning the trust that you, the members,have in us to protect your confidential financial information. In order for Mission Fed to provide you with high quality products and services, you have entrusted us with your personal information. We understand this is your information, and we accept the responsibility to protect and keep it confidential. We commit to you that we will not violate this trust, in keeping with our Mission Values principles. Today’s financial institutions possess the ability to gather information about you. This is primarily due to the use of computers and networks that have the technology to acquire and share information. Information about you is collected every time you use the Internet, buy something using a credit card, when you open new accounts or apply for a new loan, and many other activities. Mission Fed believes we are keepers of your information, and we must take measures to ensure that your information is used properly. Maintaining your trust by protecting your right to privacy is very important to Mission Fed. We want you to understand your rights regarding our collection and use of your information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we collect, how we use it, and how we protect it. We want you to know the action Mission Fed has taken to ensure the protection of your privacy.

**Information Collected by Mission Fed**  
Mission Fed obtains information about you, including but not limited to name, address, phone number and social security number, in order to conduct your trust our commitment the operations of the credit union, such as approving new accounts or loans, communicating to you the status of your accounts, presenting opportunities for you to make changes in your account relationship that would improve your ability to meet your financial goals, and satisfying government and legal requirements. This information is collected from applications, the Mission Fed web site, documents you provide us, your transaction activity with us, our affiliates or others, and third-party information services, such as consumer reporting agencies.

**Web Site Data Use**  
Mission Fed uses a common web software tool called “cookies” to retain information about your visits to our web site. “Cookies” are pieces of information, such as pages visited and options selected, that are stored in the browser of a member’s personal computer. Mission Fed only uses this information to streamline a visitor’s web experience and not for any other purpose. Mission Fed conducts online surveys to collect information from visitors to our web site. We also collect information in association with requests for products and services. This information is used to identify changes that will make the web site more useful for visitors, evaluate the value provided by our curent and future products and services, and process product and service requests. From our web site, we do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13.

Mission Fed provides many calculators on our web site to assist visitors in making financial decisions. The web site calculator tools do not collect or store any information that is entered by web visitors. We are not responsible for the data collection and practices of third parties linked to our web site.

**Information Protection & Security**  
Mission Fed uses up-to-date security technologies to safeguard your information from unauthorized access and use. Electronic connections between you and Mission Fed, for the purpose of exchanging confidential information or performing transactions (such as MissionLink), are communicated in a secure mode, encrypting information before it is transmitted so that unauthorized access over the Internet will not compromise your information. Mission Fed maintains an internal technology security policy that identifies specific procedures for securing and accessing your information, protecting the physical property that houses your information, and reporting any suspicious activity that can identify possible attempts to fraudulently access your information. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to only those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. Our employees are trained to understand and follow these policies. In addition, Mission Fed conducts frequent and regular backups of your information and utilizes redundant information practices to protect your information from being erroneously altered due to unintentional errors and equipment malfunctions. The safeguards Mission Fed deploys, as defined above, comply with federal regulations to protect your nonpublic personal information.

**Use of Member Information**  
Mission Fed does not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our members and former members to anyone, except as permitted by law. Mission Fed does not sell any personal member information. We do provide your personal information to law enforcement agencies, as required by law, and regulatory agencies, as required by state and federal regulations. These activities include subpoenas and Suspicious Activity Reporting. Mission Fed uses nonaffiliated third-party service providers to accomplish some of its business activities (such as printing statements, ordering new checks, receiving check items from the Federal Reserve Bank, ATM and point-of-sale networks for member transactions, reporting to credit bureaus, insurance companies for loan insurance protection, and mailing services), including marketing efforts on Mission Fed’s behalf. For some of these third parties, it is necessary for Mission Fed to provide them with your nonpublic personal information (acquired as disclosed above) in order for them to complete the requirements of their service. In these instances, Mission Fed requires the third-party service providers to provide common practice security and protection of your information, and they agree not to provide this information to any other entity, including their subsidiaries. This is documented in each agreement between Mission Fed and its non-affiliated third-party service providers. If you have not opted out of information sharing, Mission Fed may disclose nonpublic personal information to Mission Fed's affiliates. Former members’ (those who have closed their accounts at Mission Fed) nonpublic information is only provided to credit bureaus. This reporting assists those former members in opening new accounts and obtaining loans.

**How You Can Help**  
If you ever suspect your confidential information has been accessed improperly or the information is inaccurate, incomplete, or outdated, please inform us as soon as possible by following any of the notification options identified below in "Contacting Mission Fed."

**Notices**  
Mission Fed has developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of the steps we take to protect your information and your rights regarding the use of your information. This policy is made available to all new members at the time of opening an account at Mission Fed. If an account is opened by mail, telephone, or any other situation where a Privacy Policy cannot be delivered immediately, this Privacy Policy will be mailed within three (3) business days. Mission Fed will continue to send our Privacy Policy to you annually, or when changes are made to the policy, by separate mailing or include it with your account statement. We may send you the Privacy Policy by electronic mail provided you have given us written approval to do so, or you can retrieve a copy at your convenience via our home page at www.missionfed.com.

**Contacting Mission Fed**  
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Mission Fed:   
by calling 800-500-MFCU(6328)  
by e-mail to missionmail@missionfed.com  
or by mailing written requests to:

Mission Federal Credit Union  
Attn: Contact Center  
P.O. Box 919023  
San Diego CA 92191-9023

**Downloads**  
Privacy Policy  
Mission Federal Services LLC Privacy Policy
